https://www.monitortech.com/privacy.shtml

PRIVACY STATEMENT
( click here )
Your personal information is important to us:
Monitor recognizes that your privacy is very important to you and
that you have a right to control your personal information. We
know that
providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that
seriously.
Monitor & best practice privacy standards:
Monitor is committed to protecting your personal information. We
believe that our privacy policy is both fair and represents industry
best practice.
Monitor is committed to building on the high levels of trust that
it enjoys with its customers. Monitor will comply with any laws
introduced
to strengthen protections for consumers' privacy.
What information
we collect about you:
Monitor will not collect or monitor any personal information
about you without your consent. Only information you provide
Monitor
with directly will be collected, such as through requesting catalogs
or
registering for special access to our website. The only personal
information we collect is what you tell us about yourself. For
example, when you
fill out a request form, we collect the details you enter to enable
us to send information to you. When you answer questions about
what you would like to see we keep this information to better serve
you.
Monitor's use of "cookies":
Monitor uses "cookies" to help enhance your experience
on our website. Cookies are pieces of information that a website
transfers
to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Most
Web browsers are set to accept cookies as the default. However,
if you
do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to
refuse cookies. Cookies can also provide us with information on
how our
customers use our website so that we can continually improve
the design of the
web site. They operate as a unique identifier which helps
us to know
what our customers find interesting and useful on our website.
Using & disclosing
your personal information:
Monitor will not use or disclose any specific information about
you without your consent, unless required by law. Monitor recognizes
the trust you place in us when you give us personal information.
We will
use this information to bring you products & services which
we believe will be of benefit to you. However, we will not disclose
specific information about you to any other company (with the
exception
of authorized
Monitor representatives,
partners and service providers) without your explicit consent.
Information & Promotional
Emails:
From time to time we will send you relevant information emails
regarding new products and services available from Monitor. If
you are receiving
promotional information from Monitor and do not wish to receive
this information any longer, you may unsubscribe at any time
by following
the instructions provided in the email.
Storage & security
of your details:
Monitor will endeavor to take all reasonable steps to keep secure
any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information
accurate
and up to date. In addition, Monitor's employees and authorized
representatives are obliged to respect the confidentiality of
any personal information
held by Monitor.
However, Monitor will not be held responsible
for events arising from unauthorized access to your personal
information. We encourage you to play an important role in keeping
your personal
information secure, by maintaining the confidentiality of any
passwords and account details used on the Monitor website.
We retain personal data for only as long as necessary to provide the Services requested and thereafter for a variety of legitimate legal or business purposes.
Accessing,
changing & deleting information we keep about you:
Your trust in Monitor is very important to us. If at any time
you want to know exactly what personal information we are holding
at
any particular
time, email us. Should you wish to change personal information
that is inaccurate or out of date, you can also do this via email.
You may
even permanently remove your details from Monitor's databases.
EBC & links
to other websites:
Monitor provides links to websites outside of the Monitor portal.
These linked sites are not under the control of Monitor, and
we are not responsible
for the conduct of companies linked to our website. Before disclosing
your personal information on any other website, we advise you
to examine the privacy policies for those sites. Should you be
concerned
with
the conduct of a site which you accessed via a link from the
Monitor site, please help us to help you, by emailing us.
Monitor is PCI compliant for processing credit cards:
text and documents.
